what's going on guys welcome back to another day
in the life video i'm here with robert miller he's
a serial entrepreneur owns an eight-figure
e-commerce agency he's also an investor rob
thanks for having us yeah for sure man thanks
for coming around could you give us a little quick
intro about like what you're doing and everything you
got going on yeah sure thing so i have a
couple different businesses a lot in the digital
marketing space first one has actually just been
an agency we actually work with a lot
of entrepreneurs work with a lot of businesses
help them scale up but the other one that i've
kind of been really known for has been our e-commerce
investment company essentially where we've built brands
we've sold brands and essentially we help
people create their own stores and have exposure to ecom
let's get to it just walk in i just have
to ask i mean the library looks incredible could you
just give me a rundown of some of your favorite
books something you recommend and what are some
must reads for people out there i've been
in the books ever since i was like 17
18 years old really got into entrepreneurship because of
books so i'm like super into them the first one
i actually ever read was the 10x rule by grant
cardone i actually ended up working with him
for about seven to eight months in digital marketing
space so i always recommend you know if people
are just starting out have the right mindset so
10x rule is always you know a staple i
think that's a really foundational book and then if
you're looking for a book that's really good to read
you can go to the 10x rule website and you can
really just in entrepreneurship and wanting to get
into marketing i think the whole dot com series
by russell brunson is good as well as you
can grow rich everyone talks about you know napoleon hill
and the books that he's had yeah
they're absolutely classic that's one of my favorite
ones and something i actually revisit on an annual basis
but other than that man i mean there's a lot
of other businesses i'm really big into finance
and so the biggest ones that actually started to
shape the way that i thought about money
was first unshakable by tony robbins kind of goes
over the financial markets how they work and what
fees you want to avoid and things like that and
then i got into another
book the history of central banking
and the enslavement of mankind that one
goes over the debasing of currencies and ultimately
how we've gotten inflation and how we've actually
seen nations rise and fall and then that staples
into this one here called the fiat standard
by safedina moose who's an economic theme when it
comes to bitcoin and all that kind of stuff so i
love all this stuff too i have to ask i saw this
uh this award here you got a little two comic
club award before winning this one i had won it six
times for other people so when i was an advertising
agency and the thing with the agency space is like
you will have a client churn
at some point depending if it's priced depending
if this was what they're going through if they
didn't budget things properly that's just part of the game
so i was like you know what screw it i'm
gonna go do it and get the award for myself
and that's end of what happened we did it in about
six months we got the award and we technically got two
but we only got one on the uh i only paid for
one just to reiterate what what exactly was the
award just for people out there that don't don't
really understand what that is so click funnels is
a software essentially you know the books i was
talking about the dot com series books and
everything by russell brunson he has a software
essentially it's called click funnels and it's
a software that's basically a software that's
basically a software that's designed to help people get a
lot of money out of funnels if you do a
million dollars through just one of their funnels uh
then you actually can get an award so one
website or one landing page for us did a
million dollars you know you're working so hard throughout
the day how do you kind of like let off steam like
what do you what do you kind of do to relax and is
there anything like from a meditation standpoint that
you do to kind of clear your head first
thing i wake up anywhere between five to
six in the morning typically every morning i've been
getting into like jiu jitsu and a couple
other things recently so sometimes my body needs a
little bit more rest but uh typically it's five to
six in the morning and then i'll come out and
i'll typically just grab water you know do the
whole morning routine and then just get up and go
you know do the whole morning routine of
like protein shakes you know supplements all that
once i'm done i'll come out here i'll read i'll
meditate i even have a yoga mat sometimes if i
need to stretch out roll out and really that's it then
i'll go down we'll go on a walk just kind of
get the body moving and then during that time
usually i'm just either alone in my own thoughts
and i'm just thinking through different exercises and
stuff like that or i'll actually put on like
a podcast and i'll listen to different news
about finance or different news about marketing anything
that i want to do but the view man it
helps me to come out here decompress especially in between
meetings if i need four to five minutes just to
kind of you know let a meeting sit do a little
bit of breath work and then come outside look at the
view and then i'll go back at it if you could
spend the day with one influential figure who would
it be and why live i'd say grant cardone
he's been a pretty influential person in my
life just throughout all the different books and being
able to work for him and all that kind of stuff
it would kind of fulfill a whole prophecy if you will
in my in my book being able to work alongside
and collaborate with him that's a really big one that
i would enjoy him and ray dahlia actually ray
dahlia is you know a billionaire hedge fund guy
and i read all of his books too so
those two those would be really cool to meet
dead i'd probably go back to uh earl schoaf
jim rohn's original mentor jim rohn is known as kind
of like the father of personal development
he really made it mainstream right everyone loves
jim rohn and stuff but earl schoaf was actually
his original mentor and so if you go back and
you listen to some of his tapes obviously you
see what jim rohn has done and then what tony
robbins has done and stuff to go back to
the origin source that was really close to you know
before all the media came out and everyone
started repeating some of those you know core philosophies
but like someone that actually embodied it way
back in the day especially seeing how the dynamic
so i would love to just chat with him to see
what you know life was like back then and how those
principles were different for the sector in the end of
the era that he was in what are we doing
now like you kind of basically you just either
start your day or just sometime in the morning
kind of go out on this trail yeah in the morning
to be around like again like 6 a.m once i'm done
with kind of the stuff in the morning up the unit
i'll just come down on the trail you know i'm out
here either for personal preferences of just not
listening to anything and just kind of being in
my own headspace really thinking through ideas of where
i want to go in life or you know other
things with the business going on different issues
i try and step out to then come back
and be able to tackle it gives you a
different perspective a lot of the times when you're not
in the weeds and it's also like that time for
yourself too like i am super strict now with my
time i used to always give time to people give
time to people give time to people and at some
point there's like the diminishing returns where your
cup's not being filled and you're not even
doing the bare minimum for yourself you know with mentors
for me i was always like hey if you need
anything let me know if you need anything let me
know and i just you know provide a lot of value
that way but at some point you stack
enough responsibility in your business or in yourself
that you need to put that 30 minutes
aside for yourself in the morning or whatever you
need to do to get that 30 minutes out of your
day and then you can just go back and do whatever
that is for me it's about 30 to 40 minutes then
i get right to it in your instagram bio you have
god first written how important has faith been
to you throughout your lifetime been really important
man actually my one of my first mentors very
spiritual in regards to faith like he was very
well connected to that and attribute a lot of his
success to it and i still hop on calls them today
where in the midst of a big crisis for
him financially he gave a big chunk of money as
tithes and offerings because you know the money
and the resources that he's collected was was a
pretty pretty good change you know he doesn't have
to work anything or anymore he's set up for
generations but he still gave up a big chunk
because he knows that it's going to be better
in god's hands than his for me you know i've
had my ups and downs with faith and everything but i
think the biggest thing is instead of just
blindly going into a faith or religion like understanding
why and also what that connection means because
it's just like if you have something and it's
taken away from you now you know the value it's
the same thing if you don't pour into that for
yourself spiritually and if you even don't
go through some discovery sometimes and you just
kind of blindly accept it you don't understand
the true moral foundation of like the power of
simple scripture or simple
philosophy all right guys we just finished up on
the trail with robert he actually had to step out
real quick to take a quick phone call but when
he comes back we're going to jump into a classic hard
knock style street interview yeah we're just going
to be asking a couple questions like we typically
do like the advice he tells younger self
and how someone can become financially free and wealthy
in today's world so stay tuned and we're going
to get the shotgun excuse me sir quick question for
you if you were to go back to when you were
either high school or college what is the best piece of
advice you would tell your younger self invest
into mentors get into the room whatever it is
whether it's you don't really have a lot of money
at that time so give you know you're going to have
a lot of money at that time so give you know you're
going to have a lot of money at that time so give you
you don't really have a lot of money at that time
so give your time to the actual mentor to help them
with whatever they're doing so if they have
multiple businesses if they are making a lot
of money see how you can get in the door
what is your best piece of advice to someone wanting to
start a business in 2022 i would start
out in services especially right now everyone needs
you know everyone has problems if you can
solve those problems the digital side and making it
super sexy isn't the first place to start you
want to actually solve a problem first and then
once you figure out what that problem that you're solving
is then you can go to scale it but first
help people and that's how you can kind
of take the service businesses to the next level
next level for someone trying to scale from you
know six to seven to potentially eight or nine
figures what advice would you give to someone
who's trying to scale well i haven't hit nine
figures yet so i can't give advice there but uh
first zero to six is the skill sets six to seven
is then being able to get predictable new clients
from your new service or from your new business
and then seven to eight is following the
graph whether that's ads people numbers don't lie people
do what skillset have you seen what
separates people from the rest copywriting sales and
marketing if you can learn those three copywriting is
sales in written form sales is doing it over
the phone being able to
persuade and then third is marketing how do you
get more people to hear what you have to offer
if you were to start from zero and you had
one year to make a million dollars and your life
dependent on it what would you do high
ticket services and collaboration i would look for
networks to be able to tap into that way i don't
have to spend a lot on marketing and ads but i
would collaborate with people provide a solution
that has multiple services multiple customers at
once rather than trying to go one at a time one
two three go to a mastermind go to a network and
try and roll something out that's beneficial to all
parties i love that and what is the secret
to sales in 2022
just being authentic i think actually solving the
problem number one if you're doing that then
that's to solve it but two is uh how
are you actually gonna build that relationship over time
i think a lot of people are in it
for the transaction and it can be hard sometimes when
you're scaling out an offer to have relationships with
every single person but if you try to at least
build community and build trust and really
understand that you have their best interest
at mind or at heart that's what really matters and
they'll feel that so you just got off a call
what were you guys talking about yeah man
so just going over with our leadership call essentially
um i think the most important thing was our
leadership calls so we got a lot of updates
from our department on what's going on in the
business world uh we're just keeping up on and
we just make sure that each department's doing the
right functions and got a lot of updates with some
of the newer things we're rolling out
in our shopify department which is recurring subscriptions
and billing and things like that just leadership calls
man what what does your typical start of the
day end of the day look like so people can
kind of really capture what it's like to be a serial
entrepreneur what do you have to do on the daily basis
to be able to meet your goals and be able to
get done what you need to get done in the beginning of
starting out i was very like i was 6 a.m till 10
now to be like, yo, this is my meeting schedule
here and here. But now I wake up at around like
five to six. I'll go out for a little bit
of a morning routine. I'll go out on a walk,
listen to a podcast or just do my
own thing. I'll journal, I'll meditate. So typically in
the mornings, I'll just have a work block from
like 7 a.m. till about maybe about 11. And my
first call will be at about 11 or 12.
And then subsequent calls after that, whether that be
sales calls from time to time or partnership
and collaboration calls, then I'll essentially go into
another deep work session. Typically that's around three to
four. If I have calls that fill up the
rest of the day, then I'll stop at around five.
I'll go hit the gym around like six, six thirty,
come back, read and then, you know, go into course
material or stuff like that that I want to learn
and then go from there. I know we talked
about reading a lot with personal development, but how
big has been keeping up with, you know, just
joining into new courses and stuff, even at the
point of success where you're at now? Definitely always
in courses. I think if you think that you
know it all, you've already lost. At least for
me, when I have business problems arise and I don't
know the answer to them, I'll tap into my
resource network. We always have a library. We have Google,
we have the internet, but what's your
internal library that you can actually draw from? Those
are typically courses and a little bit of a
system that you kind of build for yourself. So
that's what I've done. That kind of wraps it up
for a day in the life with Robert Miller.
Robert, thanks so much for having us, man. Yeah. Really
appreciate your time, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Where can
everyone find you? Yeah. At the Robert J. Miller
on Instagram. But guys, I actually got another meeting,
so I need you guys to get out of here.
Sounds good, man. I'm just playing, guys. Good seeing you.